[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Bowling Hall of Fame located?", "correct_answer": "Saint Louis, MO", "incorrect_answers": ["Tucson, AZ", "Canastota, NY", "Stroudsberg, PA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flag of what country consists of a simple green field with no other features?", "correct_answer": "Libya", "incorrect_answers": ["Lebanon", "Laos", "Lithuania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which if the following is not among the 12 standard tokens used in Monopoly?", "correct_answer": "A kettle", "incorrect_answers": ["An old shoe", "An iron", "A top hat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The common name of the flower, Lilium lancifolium, is the name of a character in which childrens classic?", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Peter Pan", "incorrect_answers": ["The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", "Winnie the Pooh", "Anne of Green Gables"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Archaeological findings suggest that true glass was first invented in this country.", "correct_answer": "Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["Japan", "China", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of Willy Wonkas gloves that he wears all the time in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "White", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do you say snow in French?", "correct_answer": "neige", "incorrect_answers": ["vent", "soleil", "pluie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which English coin represented one-twentieth of a pound?", "correct_answer": "Shilling", "incorrect_answers": ["Crown", "Farthing", "Pence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is thyme tea traditionally given to women after childbirth in Jamaica?", "correct_answer": "To cause uterine contractions", "incorrect_answers": ["To induce sleep", "To stop the bleeding", "Due to a superstition"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Andys jock boyfriend in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Troy", "incorrect_answers": ["Walt", "Brandon", "Tommy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nag is slang for what animal?", "correct_answer": "Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Snake", "Newt", "Pony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular man is also known as the king of the comb over due to his hairstyle?", "correct_answer": "Robert Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Donald Trump", "Bobby Charlton", "Lou Henson"]}]